{
    "id": "bbedd3dd85bd40bb80a6ade155125c87",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "When I have guests I myself cook dinner for ……………………",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a preposition should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "themselves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When she realized her mistake she laughed at ……………………",
            "description": "The reflexive is used when the subject and the object refer to the same person.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie prevented me from entering …………………….. room.",
            "description": "The words her, his, their, your, our and my are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She yelled at ………………………… without any provocation.",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a preposition should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That is ………………………….",
            "description": "Possessive pronouns are words like mine, his, hers, theirs, ours, yours etc. They are used alone as subject complements. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. bag is this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who's",
                "Whose"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my car. Is that ………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t believe ……………………….. eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "myself",
                "my own"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I did it …………………………. as there was no one to help me.",
            "description": "The emphatic is used to emphasize an idea.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself",
                "myselves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Please do it …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yourself",
                "you",
                "your"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I cut ………………………… while shaving.",
            "description": "The reflexive is used when the subject and the object refer to the same person.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself",
                "myselves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She admired ……………………………. in the mirror.",
            "description": "The reflexive is used when the subject and the object refer to the same person.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself",
                "herselves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}